// To extract image from public folder
export const ARTISTS = [
  ["eternalgosh", "Eternal Gosh"],
  ["RZarni", "R Zarni"],
  ["bigbag", "Big Bag"],
  ["layphyu", "Lay Phyu"],
];

// For payment information
export const PAYMENT_INFO = [
  {
    type: "Daily",
    price: "99",
    description:
      '"For a single day, enjoy uninterrupted music, just like clockwork."',
    source: ["dollar", "mptLogo"],
  },
  {
    type: "Weekly",
    price: "599",
    description: '"Seven full days of ad-free, premium music streaming."',
    source: ["dollar", "mptLogo", "kbzPay"],
  },
  {
    type: "Monthly",
    price: "1,999",
    description: '"A month of unlimited music at your command."',
    source: ["kbzPay"],
  },
  {
    type: "Yearly",
    price: "19,999",
    description: '"Commit to a year of premium music streaming."',
    source: ["kbzPay"],
  },
];

// For Q&A
export const SUPPORT_DETAILS = [
  {
    key: 0,
    question: "What is Melo?",
    answer:
      "Melo is an online music platform which offers special features like storing and streaming services unlike other local music applications. Melo is dedicated to building a strong bond between various artists and users and exposed to different types of genres, albums, ringtunes, music videos and live streaming at one place.",
  },
  {
    key: 1,
    question: "Can I sign up Melo with phone sim cards?",
    answer:
      "Unfortunately, Melo can be accessed with only MPT sim cards at the moment. The user can easily sign up to Melo with an MPT phone sim card and you may receive a verification code via 8736 within 1 minute. If there is any delayed process or you don't receive the verification code, you can contact MPT call centre at 106.",
  },
  {
    key: 2,
    question: "Is premium subscription auto-renewal?",
    answer:
      "If you subscribe to a premium subscription with MPT phone bill, the subscription will be auto-renewal. You can send OFF to 8736 if you wish to stop purchasing the premium plan. Notice that there is no renewal process if you use other payment methods like KBZpay and my coins.",
  },
  {
    key: 3,
    question: "Where can I see the lyrics?",
    answer:
      "Lyrics icon will appear beside the songs and you can tap to see the full version of lyrics when you upgrade to premium.",
  },
  {
    key: 4,
    question: "Can I download the songs and albums?",
    answer:
      'You can listen to the songs offline if you buy an album or like songs when you upgrade to premium. You can watch your purchased albums and liked songs on the “Library" page easily at one click.',
  },
  {
    key: 5,
    question: "How do I purchase a Melo Premium Subscription?",
    answer:
      "To buy a premium subscription, go to your profile, click premium and subscribe. Next select your preferred payment method and choose a plan you like and then congratulations now you are a premium user. Notice that when you upgrade with KBZpay, you can only choose a monthly plan at the present.",
  },
  {
    key: 6,
    question: "What benefits can I get from Melo Premium Subscription?",
    answer: `You will never be interrupted by any ads while playing music. You can always listen to songs with high quality while having access to download songs and listen offline. You can also create your own customised playlists and enjoy endless music with no limits.`,
  },
  {
    key: 7,
    question: "What types of language options are there is Melo App?",
    answer:
      "Melo App is available in English and Burmese languages for both application and website currently. We are also trying to be able to access multiple languages in the future to connect with more people worldwide.",
  },
  {
    key: 8,
    question: "Are music videos available on Melo platform?",
    answer:
      'Yes, you can choose the “Live & Videos” option at the top of the "Discover" page and watch endless videos comfortably from the Melo app.',
  },
  {
    key: 9,
    question: "How can I know new updates about Melo?",
    answer:
      "Open Notifications in your app settings and receive up-to-date songs and news from Melo everyday.",
  },
  {
    key: 10,
    question: "How to buy ringtunes via Melo?",
    answer:
      "Open any songs or albums that you want to set ringtunes on your phone and click the caller phone icon on the page. Then choose your sim card type and select your favourite part of the song and send a code message.",
  },
];
